"My Secret Vampire"
(Episode 8)
Hmm.
So it's not really a cult...
Your dream isn't to be a priest, is it?
Do you like garlic?
Are you good at reading people?
Juwon probably doesn't eat
things like ginger or garlic...
Not being able to eat
those things is a bit...
Is anyone here?
Is this what you wanted to do?
You really don't want to
take this picture, do you?
You look like you could
shoot lasers from your eyes.
There's something wrong with the camera.
I'm keeping this one, then.
You should be more honest with yourself.
I try to do that every time.
Even though it always feels
like I'm the one who loses.
But I don't mind.
Because I'm not good
at hiding my feelings...
You weren't scared that I'd find out.
You were scared that I'd get hurt.
But I still like you.
What am I supposed to do...?
Juwon?
I've missed you so much.
Dongha.
Why did you come all the way
here in this cold, dressed like that?
Because I was in a hurry to see you.
It was farther than I thought.
You.
What were you thinking,
coming all the way out here?
A vampire, living right
in the middle of the city...!
I was thinking.
Maybe I should just expose all of you.
Just kidding.
Jeez.
What are you doing?
I thought you couldn't sleep on the floor.
I'll just sleep here.
You're being so nice to me all of a sudden.
I'm not used to it.
Just sleep here with me.
Huh?
It's not like we haven't
slept in the same bed before.
When was this?
The day of my birthday party.
But you look like you're about to cry.
Because none of my friends were my age.
They were all old enough
to be my grandparents.
I see.
When I was about your age,
I used to cry a lot, too.
Why?
Because I didn't want to drink blood...
I didn't even know I
was a vampire back then.
Is that even possible?
When the Father first found me,
he said I was very sick.
So he turned me into a
vampire to save my life.
I see...
Oh, right...
That day...
I thought your wound was poisoned,
- I was trying to suck out the poison...
- Hey...
Do you feel very tired right now?
No.
Why?
When I was little,
I loved looking at the sky from here.
What star is that?
Just because I live in the country
doesn't make me an expert on stars.
I don't know. It could be space junk.
But who cares?
It's beautiful, and
that's all that matters.
That's enough.
It is beautiful.
Huh?
Hey, how do you have this...?
It found its way back to its owner.
Why does it look like this?
Ah.
Silver isn't good for us.
- Then take it off!
- It's fine.
Why are you still wearing it?
I told you, it's fine.
Here, give it to me.
I like you.
Dongha.
Actually,
I've regretted
leaving like that the other day.
I couldn't stop myself
from falling for you...
I was worried that you
might get hurt because of me.
I was so scared.
I want to be honest, like you said.
That's why I gathered
the courage to come here.
Why aren't you saying anything?
My answer.
Let's go home together.
Everyone misses you.
Can I really go back?
Of course.
It's our home.
You're alone?
What?
What's with that reaction?
It's nothing.
It's just that...
I got my hopes up for nothing.
What were you hoping for?
Was it... me?
Dongha!
- We missed you like crazy!
- Dongha! We really missed you.
I know, I know.
Didn't you miss us at all?
We've been waiting for you for so long.
I know, right?
(Contract for Rental Tenancy Extension)
Let's all get along!
That won't be necessary.
As long as we respect
each other's privacy...
Here we go again.
What do you even mean by "privacy"?
Do you vampires have
some big secret to hide?
I wasn't talking about myself.
I was talking about you guys.
You guys.
You'd better not let me catch you.
Hey, we're not scumbags.
Yeah, really.
Our dear Dongha. I'm going
to take good care of you.
Hey, get away from him.
Hey! Let go of him!
You seem to really like him.
Hey, guys!
I'm hungry.
Let's eat!
Wow.
This is the taste I remember.
I could cry.
Hey.
Don't tell me this is the only reason
you wanted me back.
Hey, that's hurtful.
Whatever you want to eat, Dongha,
we'll make it for you, three meals a day!
That might be a bit much...
After we eat, you guys
want to play some basketball?
No?
Gyumin hates basketball.
Doesn't he just hate it
because he sucks at it?
Yeah... He's not exactly athletic.
What are you talking about?
I'm definitely better than any human.
Hey, I don't like the sound of that
"human" remark. We'll see who wins!
Okay! Bring it on!
Cha Eun-ho, you're on our team, right?
Hey, you can't just claim Eun-ho like that.
That's cheating!
Han Dongha.
What about me?
Eun-ho! I'm definitely better than Gyumin.
That's nonsense. He's terrible.
I'm speechless.
You really want to play?
Of course.
You have to be on my side.
Got it?
Of course. I'm always on your side.
It's so hot.
But...
what did you mean by
what you said back then?
What did I say?
"How could I ever...
with someone like you..."
Isn't that what you said?
What about it?
No.
How could I...
fall for someone like you?
That's probably what you meant, right?
Are... you crazy?
Then what was it?
I don't know. Just stop asking.
I need some time to think...
Then let's find out.
Huh?
What those words...
really meant.
Let's find out right now.
Having fun?
How about this?
Hey! We're in a library.
So what?
Jeez...
Do you like me that much?
Yes.
Since when?
Hmm...
From the very beginning,
I found myself strangely drawn to you.
Whenever you were out of my sight,
I'd always find myself looking for you.
"My Secret Vampire"